## Jaehong Yoon

Contact

KAIST, South Korea

Information

E-MAIL: jaehong.yoon@kaist.ac.kr

LINKS: HOMEPAGE, GOOGLE SCHOLAR, TWITTER

RESEARCH INTERESTS

My research interest mainly focuses on developing lifelong and meta-cognitive algorithms for tackling practical challenges in deploying on-device artificial general intelligence system to various real-world application domains. I've been focusing on bridging my research experience to relevant research areas, such as open-world problems, online/streaming learning, reinforcement learning, multimodal, and language models. I currently focus on the following topics:

- Lifelong Machine learning: Online Learning, Continual Learning
- Collective Machine Intelligence: On-device Learning, Federated Learning
- Learning with incomplete data: Un-/Self-supervised Learning, Coreset Selection
- Low-resource learning: Network Compression, Quantization

**EDUCATION** 

#### KAIST, Daejeon, South Korea

Ph.D. student, School of Computing,

Aug 2018 - Current

- Machine Learning and Artificial Intelligence (MLAI) Lab
- Adviser: Sung Ju Hwang
- Area of Study: Machine Learning
- Anticipated Graduation Date: Feb 2023

UNIST, Ulsan, South Korea

M.S., Computer Science,

Aug 2016 - Feb 2018

- Thesis: Combined Group and Exclusive Sparsity for Deep Neural Networks
- Adviser: Sung Ju Hwang
- Area of Study: Machine Learning

B.S., Computer Science Engineering,

Mar 2012 - Aug 2016

• Biological Science Minor

RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

#### Weizmann Institute of Science, Rehovot, Israel

VISITING STUDENT

Oct 2022 - Nov 2022

• Host: Prof. Yonina Eldar

Microsoft Research, Beijing, China

Research Internship

Nov 2021 - Apr 2022

• Visual Computing Group

• Mentor: Yue Cao

MLAI Lab., KAIST, Daejeon, South Korea

CONTRACT RESEARCH SCIENTIST

Feb 2018 - Aug 2018

AITRICS, Seoul, South Korea

RESEARCH INTERNSHIP

Mar 2018 - May 2018

#### CONFERENCE PUBLICATIONS

\*: equal contribution

# [C9] Bitwidth Heterogeneous Federated Learning with Progressive Weight Dequantization

Jaehong Yoon\*, Geon Park\*, Wonyong Jeong, and Sung Ju Hwang International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML) 2022, Baltimore, USA

## [C8] Forget-free Continual Learning with Winning Subnetworks Haeyong Kang\*, Rusty J. L. Mina\*, Sultan R. H. Madjid, Jaehong Yoon, Mark Hasegawa-Johnson, Sung Ju Hwang, and Chang D. Yoo International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML) 2022, Baltimore, USA

# [C7] Rethinking the Representational Continuity: Towards Unsupervised Continual Learning

Divyam Madaan, Jaehong Yoon, Yuanchun Li, Yunxin Liu, and Sung Ju Hwang International Conference on Machine Learning (ICLR) 2022, Virtual Oral Presentation (Acceptance Rate = 54/3391 = 1.6%)

## [C6] Online Coreset Selection for Rehearsal-based Continual Learning Jaehong Yoon, Divyam Madaan, Eunho Yang, and Sung Ju Hwang International Conference on Machine Learning (ICLR) 2022, Virtual

## [C5] Federated Continual Learning with Weighted Inter-client Transfer Jaehong Yoon\*, Wonyong Jeong\*, Giwoong Lee, Eunho Yang, and Sung Ju Hwang International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML) 2021, Virtual

## [C4] Federated Semi-supervised Learning with Inter-Client Consistency & Disjoint Learning

Wonyong Jeong, **Jaehong Yoon**, Eunho Yang, and Sung Ju Hwang International Conference on Learning Representations (ICLR) 2021, Virtual

## [C3] Scalable and Order-robust Continual Learning with Additive Parameter Decomposition

Jaehong Yoon, Saehoon Kim, Eunho Yang, and Sung Ju Hwang International Conference on Learning Representations (ICLR) 2020, Addis ababa, Ethiopia, Virtual

## [C2] Lifelong Learning with Dynamically Expandable Networks Jaehong Yoon, Eunho Yang, Jeongtae Lee, and Sung Ju Hwang International Conference on Learning Representations (ICLR) 2018, Vancouver, Canada

## [C1] Combined Group and Exclusive Sparsity for Deep Neural Networks Jaehong Yoon and Sung Ju Hwang International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML) 2017, Sydney, Australia

#### Preprints

[P5] On the Soft-Subnetwork for Few-shot Class Incremental Learning Haeyong Kang, Jaehong Yoon, Sultan Rizky Hikmawan Madjid, Sung Ju Hwang, Chang D. Yoo Submitted, 2022.

#### [P4] BiTAT: Neural Network Binarization with Task-dependent Aggregated Transformation

Geon Park\*, **Jaehong Yoon\***, Haiyang Zhang, Xing Zhang, Sung Ju Hwang, and Yonina C. Eldar Submitted, arXiv:2207.01394, 2022.

#### [P3] Personalized Subgraph Federated Learning

Jinheon Baek\*, Wonyong Jeong\*, Jiongdao Jin, **Jaehong Yoon**, and Sung Ju Hwang Submitted, arXiv:2206.10206, 2022.

## [P2] Rapid Structural Pruning of Neural Networks with Set-based Task-Adaptive Meta-Pruning

Minyoung Song, **Jaehong Yoon**, Eunho Yang, and Sung Ju Hwang arXiv:2006.12139, 2020.

[P1] Adaptive Network Sparsification with Dependent Beta-Bernoulli Dropout Juho Lee, Saehoon Kim, Jaehong Yoon, Haebeom Lee, Eunho Yang, and Sung Ju Hwang arXiv:1805.10896, 2018.

### Workshop Presentations

## [W2] Federated Semi-supervised Learning with Inter-client Consistency Wonyong Jeong, Jaehong Yoon, Eunho Yang, and Sung Ju Hwang ICML Workshop on Federated Learning for User Privacy and Data Confidentiality, ICML 2020, Long Presentation, Best Student Paper Award

[W1] Federated Continual Learning with Weighted Inter-client Transfer Jaehong Yoon\*, Wonyong Jeong\*, Giwoong Lee, Eunho Yang, and Sung Ju Hwang ICML Workshop on Lifelong Machine Learning, ICML 2020

## PATENTS (US ONLY)

Method and Apparatus with Neural Network and Training **Jaehong Yoon**, Saehoon Kim, Eunho Yang, and Sung Ju Hwang US 20210256374 A1, Aug 2021

Electronic Apparatus and Method for Re-learning Trained Model **Jaehong Yoon**, Eunho Yang, Jeongtae Lee, and Sung Ju Hwang US 20180357539 A1, Dec 2018

### REVIEWER SERVICES

#### International Conferences

- 2022 Conference on Lifelong Learning Agents (Collas)
- 2019 2022 International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML)
- 2019 2022 International Conference on Learning Representations (ICLR)
- 2018 2022 Neural Information Processing System (NeurIPS)
- 2020 International Joint Conferences on Artificial Intelligence (IJCAI)
- 2020 Association for the Advancement of Artificial Intelligence (AAAI)

### International Journals

- 2022 Journal of Artificial Intelligence Research (JAIR)
- 2020, 2022 IEEE Transactions on Neural Networks and Learning Systems (TNNLS)
- 2021 IEEE Transactions on Pattern Analysis and Machine Intelligence (TPAMI)

- 2021 IEEE/ACM Transactions on Networking (ToN)
- 2020 Neural Networks

### AWARDS NAVER Ph.D. Fellowship Award, 2017

#### INVITED TALKS

REPRESENTATIONAL CONTINUITY FOR UNSUPERVISED CONTINUAL LEARNING

• Korea Computer Congress (KCC), 2022

LIFELONG LEARNING WITH DYNAMICALLY EXPANDABLE NETWORKS

- Samsung SDS, 2019
- Tech. Talk from NAVER Corp., 2018
- Tech. Open Connect (T-T.O.C) from SK-Telecom, 2018

COMBINED GROUP AND EXCLUSIVE SPARSITY FOR DEEP NEURAL NETWORKS

• Korea Software Congress (KSC), 2017

#### References

- Prof. Sung Ju Hwang, Professor, KAIST Email: sjhwang82@kaist.ac.kr
- Prof. Eunho Yang, Associate Professor, KAIST Email: eunhoy@kaist.ac.kr
- Prof. Yonina Eldar, Professor, Weizmann Institute of Science, Israel Email: yonina.eldar@weizmann.ac.il
- Dr. Yue Cao, Senior Researcher, Mircosoft Research Asia Email: yue.cao@microsoft.com